<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">UOIT / DC Booking</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Today</string>
    <string name="loading_video">Loading video</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Tomorow</string>
    <string name="refresh_label">Refresh</string>
    <string name="updates"></string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="about_me_monologue"><p>Hey, thanks for checking out this page.\n\nI\'m a UOIT Comp Sci student and this is my first android app. 
        Sorry if there are any bugs but I hope you find it useful since the old booking system is so archaic.\n\n Check
        out my blog at <a href="www.ObjectiveTruth.ca">www.ObjectiveTruth.ca</a> and read up on the adventures of getting this thing off the ground.
       	If you have any comments or suggestions feel free to comment there.\n\n

        Last thing, sorry about the ads, but it took about 4 months to get all this working, and I figure if you found it useful,
        you wouldn\'t mind seeing a few ads here and there. Hope i\'m not wrong. \n\nIf you do hate it enough you can disable them all with the button above.\n\n
        Cheers!
        </p>
        </string>
   <string name="about_me_word">
       About
   </string>
   <string name="qrcode_success_button">QR Code</string>
   <string name="qrcode_return_message">Return</string>
   <string name="why_upgrade">Upgrade Now to get these features:\n\n
		&#8226; Remove Ads\n
		&#8226; Add Booking to Calendar\n
		&#8226; QR Code Creation/Sharing\n
		&#8226; Virtual hug for supporting my app
	</string>
   <string name="debug_title">Debug</string>
   <string name="eula">None</string>
   <string name="networkerrordialogue">Couldn\'t access the internet, try double checking the settings and try again.</string>
   <string name="giphy_search_url">http://api.giphy.com/v1/gifs/random?api_key=dc6zaTOxFJmzC&amp;tag=happy</string>
   <string name="groupNameValidateError">Must be between 2 and 8 characters long</string>
   <string name="groupCodeValidateError">Unique 4 character code for your group</string>
   <string name="title_activity_feedback">Shake to Bug Report</string>
   <string name="iab_setup_fail">Error: Unable to Setup Purchase Sync</string>
   <string name="iab_query_inventory_fail">Error: Unable to Sync Purchases</string>
   <string name="thanks_for_buying">Thanks for buying!\n\n You rock!</string>
   <string name="upgrade_coming"><u><b>Premium version with added Features Coming Soon!</b></u>\n\n
       -Randomized Group Code\n
       -Bookings/Semester Used Counter\n
       -Disabling of ads\n
       -Share a booking via QR code\n
       -Calendar Sharing\n
       </string>
   <string name="qrreceive_coming">QR Booking Sharing Coming Soon!</string>
   <string name="credentials_instructions">Password is the same used for your <b>laptop (UOIT)</b> or <b>DC Connect (DC).</b> \n \n
       It cannot be longer than 15 characters and must be alphanumeric.
       </string>
   <string name="remember_me_text">Remember Me</string>
   <string name="calendardescription">Group Study Room booked using the UOIT / DC Library Booking App.\n\n
       Available in the <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.objectivetruth.uoitlibrarybooking">Goole Play Store</a>\n
       (play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.objectivetruth.uoitlibrarybooking)\n\n
       For additional information regarding booking guidelines/policies go to \n
       https://rooms.library.dc-uoit.ca/studyrooms/instruction.aspx
       </string>
   <string name="qrreceive_instructions">Scan a QR Code generated by this applicaion to be taken directly to the appropriate time/room\n\n
        A UOIT / DC Booking QR Code can be displayed after creating a pending or completed booking using this app.
        </string>
   <string name="invalid_qr_dialog_title">Invalid Code</string>
   <string name="invalid_qr_dialog_message">\nQR Receive only works when used with a QR Code generated when you book a room. \n\nCheck the instructions behind this dialog box for more info.\n</string>
   <string name="showcaseIntro">
       \nThis is an unofficial app and is in no way affiliated nor endorsed by the University of Ontario Institute of Technology (UOIT) or Durham College (DC).\n\n
        For more information see the About section\n
   </string>
    <string name="policiesHint">
        If this is your first time reserving a room at the school, you should check out the policies section for information on requirements, how to borrow markers, semester limits, etc.
    </string>
    <string name="my_account_frag_title">My Account</string>
    <string name="my_account_bookings_left_word">Bookings Left\u0020\u0020 </string>
    <string name="my_account_logged_in_as_word">Logged in as\u0020\u0020</string>
    <string name="error_please_log_in">Log in first to book a room</string>
    <string name="error_room_no_exist_comment">Room hasn\'t been inputted into the system yet, developer has been contacted, sorry about that!</string>
    <string name="error_shared_pref_values_incorrect">Couldn\'t retrieve your user data, try logging out and back in</string>
    <string name="guidelines_policies_para1">
            Your student ID can be used only once per day to a maximum of 20 bookings per term for group study room bookings.\n\n
            Bookings are available for a maximum of 2 hours per day.\n\n
		    Bookings can be made one day in advance.\n\n
		    Bookings for tomorrow will open at 10:00 A.M. today.\n\n
		    Booking cannot be made or changed five minutes before the start time.\n\n
		    When a group completes a booking, all incomplete reservations associated with the same time/room are voided. If your reservation has been voided, you may re-use your student ID to reserve or complete a booking for the same day.\n\n
		    Your Library Account must be in good standing in order to reserve a room.\n\n
		    The booking system will not accept passwords longer than 10 characters and all characters must be alphanumeric.
    </string>
    <string name="guidelines_policies_para2">
        	It is the intent of the system to set the maximum for a single group\'s bookings to 4 hours/day. Attempts to monopolize group study rooms will be considered a breach of the Building Use Guideline. The library reserves the right to cancel bookings and /or suspend booking privileges in violation of this, or any other library guideline.\n\n
		    Bookings may be forfeited for rooms occupied by fewer than the required number of persons to book the room.\n\n
		    If a room is vacant after 15 minutes of booking time, the booking is void and the room is free for use until the next reservation.\n\n
		    Students using the group study rooms are responsible for any damage that may occur.\n\n
		    Eating in group study rooms may result in suspension of group study room booking privileges.\n\n
		    Photo ID is required for the loan of whiteboard markers and Ethernet cables from the Circulation desk.\n\n
		    The rooms are intended for organized groups\'; individuals should not join a group unless they have a prior affiliation with that group - the original booker is the owner of the booking and can ask any joiners to leave the booking or the room.
    </string>
    <string name="secret_tke_message_1_more">One more...</string>
    <string name="secret_tke_message_success">Cheers!</string>
    <string name="book_cell_description">Available \nUn-contested</string>
    <string name="joinorleave_cell_description">Available \nContested</string>
    <string name="viewleaveorjoin_cell_description">Not Available\nJoin/leave only</string>
    <string name="tooltip_groupcode">Any unique 4 character combination</string>
    <string name="tooltip_password">fes</string>
    <string name="gcm_notification_title">UOIT / DC Booking Notification</string>

</resources>
